emaze.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy - emaze

(the “Privacy Policy” or “Policy”)  
Last updated: May 23, 2013.

[Capitalized terms used hereunder and not otherwise defined shall have the meaning ascribed to them in the emaze Terms of Use available on the Web Site.]

## Definitions

www.emaze.com (the “ **Web Site** ”) is owned and operated by Visual Software Systems Ltd.

The terms “ **emaze** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ”, “ **our** ” and “ **ours** ” when used in this Privacy Policy means Visual Software Systems Ltd. which includes all its parents, subsidiaries, divisions, branches, and affiliates.

The terms “ **you** ”, “ **your** ” and “ **yours** ” when used in this Privacy Policy means any user of the Web Site.  
The term “ **Personal Data** ” refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, date of birth, e-mail address or mailing address, passwords, and any other personal information submitted by you through the Site. The term “ **Presentation Data** ” refers to Users’ presentations stored on the Web Site servers.

This Privacy Policy describes emaze’s current policies and practices with regard to Personal Data collected by emaze through the Web Site. By accessing the Site, submitting information and/or registering to the Web Site, you consent to this Privacy Policy. You may not use the Site and/or submit any information if you do not agree to any of the terms hereunder.

## Collection of Personal Data Including E-Mail Addresses

emaze takes your privacy seriously. We respect and protect the privacy of our users and take appropriate steps to safeguard your personal information.  
We collect the information you give us when you visit our Web Site and use it when you request to be contacted. You may, through the Web Site, register to receive additional information (e.g. newsletters) from us, or to use one of our services (e.g. downloading and using our mobile services and applications). When you register, we ask you for contact information like your name, postal address and e-mail address.

We sometimes supplement the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. For instance, if inaccurate postal or zip codes are received, we will use third party software to fix them.

## emaze Email Marketing Communication Policy

emaze sends promotional email only to:

• Registered Users;  
• People who have given consent to emaze to receive promotional email;  
• People on rented email lists who have given permission to the list owner to receive third-party promotional email;  
• All of the abovementioned who have not opted out after having received promotional email from us.

In each promotional email, we provide an easy and clear way to opt out of future emaze email. Opt-out requests using the opt-out link in our emails are processed automatically and go into effect immediately. Opt-out requests sent to the following email info at emaze.com are processed within 10 business days. When sending email to rented email lists, we suppress addresses of those people who have opted out of emaze email in the past.

We always disclose our identity in mass email communications.

We never use deceiving header information or subject lines.

We never send mass, promotional email to email addresses “harvested” from websites.

We never, under any circumstances, rent or sell email addresses to any other company or individual.

When coordinating with our resellers for the purpose of follow-up on sales inquiries made to us, we provide full contact information of the inquirer to the reseller, including email address, so the reseller can follow up on the inquiry.

Our marketing email policy and practice fully conforms to the United States Federal “CAN SPAM” act of 2003 and the Israeli applicable statues such as the Protection of Privacy Law 5741-1981. Note that some regions such as the European Union, have different email laws and guidelines, and emaze aims to conform to local laws in those cases. We welcome and encourage your thoughts on this policy at: info at emaze.com.

## Use of Personal Data

We process your Personal Data only for specific and limited purposes. We ask only for data that is adequate, relevant and not excessive for those purposes.  
Some of these purposes include the following:  
• We may contact you occasionally to inform you of new services we will be providing, or special offers, events or articles we think will be of interest to you.  
• We may send you regular updates by e-mail on emaze organized or related events.  
• We may send you requested information and promotional material.  
• We may use your Personal Data for marketing purposes and market research.  
• We may use your Personal Data internally to help us improve our products and services and to help resolve any problems.

## Disclosure of Your Personal Data

We do not share, sell or distribute your Personal Data with unrelated third parties, except under these limited circumstances:

Personal Data may occasionally be transferred to third parties who act for or on behalf of emaze, or in connection with the business of emaze for further processing in accordance with the purposes for which the data was originally collected or for purposes to which you have subsequently consented. For example, sometimes a third party may have access to your Personal Data in order to handle our mailings on our behalf.

We may share or transfer the information in our databases to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or this Web Site, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event.

Where appropriate, before disclosing Personal Data to a third party, we contractually require the third party to take adequate precautions to protect that data.

## Use of Presentation Data

Presentation Data of users is stored “in the cloud” on various servers (currently, we use Microsoft Azure). Presentations that are designated as public presentations might be indexed in search engines (i.e. google) and may be seen by anyone who has access to the internet. Please see our Terms of Use for more on the distinction between Presentation Data designated as public and designated as private. We take appropriate protection measures to ensure that Presentation Data which is designated by you as private will not be accessible except to you and those authorized by you.

## Anonymous Data Collected Through This Web Site

In addition to the information we collect as described above, we use technology to collect anonymous information about the use of our Web Site. This technology does not identify you personally; it simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of our Web Site (such as usage habits, frequency, duration and so on).

We use this anonymous data to improve the content and functionality of this Web Site and our e-mail updates, to better understand our customers and markets, and to improve our products and services.

## Cookies

In order to collect the anonymous data described in the preceding paragraph, we may use “cookies” that collect the first level domain name of the user and the date and time you accessed this Web Site. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters. This information is sent to your computer when you use the Web Site and it’s stored on your computer, subject to your cookies storage preferences, so that we can uniquely identify a user’s browser.

We use cookies to help us remember and process, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about Web Site traffic so that we can offer a better Web Site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our Site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web Site. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on a network, or in this case, the Internet. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.

We may also use cookies and similar tools to customize the content and advertising you receive based on the Personal Data you have provided. Personal Data you provide in structured profile fields or questions, information you add to open-ended profile fields and questions and other information about you may also be used to customize the online ads you encounter to those we believe are aligned with your interests. The information used for this feature does not provide your personal information or identify you as an individual to third parties.

## User Communications

When you send email or other communication to emaze, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

## Links to Other Web Sites

This Privacy Policy applies only to www.emaze.com and to other emaze URLs through or from which you have reached this Web Site. This Web Site contains hyperlinks to web sites that are not operated by emaze. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party web sites or any association with their operators. We do not control these web sites and are not responsible for their data or privacy practices. We urge you to review any privacy policy and terms of use posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal data about yourself.

## Information Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. Nevertheless, these security measures cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with personal information. Therefore emaze shall not be liable for any damages caused by unauthorized access to a User’s personal account.

Access to Personal Data is for restricted to designated emaze employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Transfer of Data Abroad

emaze is a global enterprise and uses various servers in different countries to store data and information. Due the nature of storage in the “cloud” Personal Data may be transferred, from time to time, from one database in a certain country to a database in another country. We will ensure that data will always remain adequately protected.

Of course, the Internet is made up of a large number of international connections. If you are visiting this Web Site from a country other than the country in which our servers are located (to the extent a single country can be identified), the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this Web Site and communicating electronically with us, you consent to these transfers.

## Special Note for Parents and Children Under Age 18

The site you are visiting is a general audience site. The Web Site is not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, he or she should contact us. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from people under 18. If we become aware that a person under 18 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files.  
If you are under 18, do not attempt to provide us any information about yourself.

## Changes to This Policy

This Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice on the Web Site. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its Last Updated date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Policy in an archive for your review.

## Questions

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about the way we process your Personal Data, please contact us by e-mailing us at info at [info@emaze.com](mailto:info@emaze.com)
